<node>
    <node>
        <title>Household Survey on Internet Access</title>
        <date>Thursday, October 27, 2016 - 10:02am</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                <strong>Dear KUSD Parent/Guardian,</strong>
            </p>
            <p>
                More and more work that students do at school is Internet-based. Students without Internet access at home are often unable to do their homework. The equity gap that this situation creates is a serious problem for these students.
            </p>
            <p>
                The Wisconsin Public Services Commission (PSC) is conducting a statewide survey to gather information about residential Internet access throughout the state. The survey gives families the opportunity to tell service providers if they need better or more affordable Internet access – or don’t have access at all.
            </p>
            <p>
                The survey, located at
                <strong>
                    <a href="https://www.research.net/r/WI_PSC_broadband_survey">https://www.research.net/r/WI_PSC_broadband_survey</a>
                </strong>
                , takes about 5 minutes to complete.
            </p>
            <p>
                You may also take the survey by phone (toll free 877-360-2973). It is especially important to take the survey, so that PSC and Internet providers know the location of all households that do not have high-quality, affordable Internet access.
            </p>
            <p>
                Please take advantage of this opportunity for your families’ voices to be heard regarding broadband!
            </p>
            <p></p>
            <hr/>
            <p></p>
            <p>
                <strong>Estimados Padres/Tutores KUSD,</strong>
            </p>
            <p>
                Más y más trabajo están llevando a cabo los estudiantes por medio del internet. Los estudiantes sin acceso a internet muy a menudo no pueden completar sus tareas. Esta brecha de equidad de esta situación está creando un problema muy serio para estos estudiantes.
            </p>
            <p>
                La Comisión de Servicio Público de Wisconsin (PSC) Está conduciendo una encuesta a nivel de estado, para obtener información tocante al acceso residencial de internet en todo el estado. La encuesta da oportunidad a familias de informar a los proveedores de servicio, de la gran necesidad de mejor o mejor accesibilidad a bajo costo de internet– o no tienen acceso en absoluto.
            </p>
            <p>
                La encuesta se encuentra en
                <strong>
                    <a href="https://www.research.net/r/WI_PSC_broadband_survey">https://www.research.net/r/WI_PSC_broadband_survey</a>
                </strong>
                , y solo le toma 5 minutos para completar.
            </p>
            <p>
                Usted también puede completar la encuesta por medio del teléfono (llamada gratis al 877-360-2973). Participar de esta encuesta es especialmente importante para que los proveedores de internet y PSC se informen del área donde las familias que no cuentan con internet de alta-calidad, y acceso de internet a bajo costo.
            </p>
            <p>
                Por favor aproveche esta oportunidad para que sea escuchada la voz de su familia respecto internet de banda ancha!
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>Equus opens November 3</title>
        <date>Tuesday, October 25, 2016 - 3:56pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                KUSD Theatre Arts is set to bring “Equus” to stage on Friday, Nov. 3, in the Tremper High School studio theatre, 8560 26th Ave. Tickets are $12 for general admission, $10 for senior citizens and $5 for students and staff.
            </p>
            <p>Show dates are:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Nov. 3 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 4 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 5 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 10 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 11 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 12 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                For more information, please contact Nic Cicerale at
                <a href="mailto:nciceral@kusd.edu">nciceral@kusd.edu</a>
                .
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>Annual Jazz Festival slated for early November</title>
        <date>Monday, October 24, 2016 - 12:02pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                The Kenosha Unified School District Department of Fine Arts, in collaboration with the Kenosha Band Boosters and Dave Sturino of Hansen’s Pool and Spa, will present the Annual Jazz Festival on Saturday, Nov. 12, 2016, at Indian Trail High School and Academy, 6800 60th St. The public is welcome to attend all activities leading up to the evening performance.
            </p>
            <p>
                Students will be involved in performance sessions with guest artists and clinicians Friday afternoon and Saturday morning. Festival activities will conclude with a public performance at 6:30 p.m. featuring all KUSD jazz ensembles and the KUSD alumni/staff ensemble. Tickets for the evening performance are $8 (all seats are reserved) and can be purchased at
                <a href="http://www.kusd.edu/finearts">www.kusd.edu/finearts</a>
                .
            </p>
            <p>
                This year’s guest artist, Sal Lozano, is a Southern California native and acclaimed saxophone performer. He is a featured member of bands led by such notable composers as Johnny Mandel, Tom Kubis, and can be heard with Gordon Goodwin's critically acclaimed Grammy Award Winning Big Phat Band. A few of the artists Lozano has recorded with include Paul McCartney, Natalie Cole, Christina Aguilera, Lady Gaga, Stevie Wonder, Lalo Schifrin, Brian McKnight, Michael Buble, Barbra Streisand, Joey DeFrancesco and Maynard Ferguson.
            </p>
            <p>
                Lozano has been a member of the Dancing with the Stars house band, the American Idol house band, and the Academy Awards Orchestra, along with holding numerous other television and commercial credits. He has also performed at the Gala for the President at Ford's Theatre in Washington D.C. and as a soloist with the Pacific Symphony, The San Diego Symphony and the Los Angeles Philharmonic. He can also be heard on numerous movie soundtracks including Straight Outa Compton, The Secret Life of Pets, Joy, Ice Age 5, National Treasure, Legally Blonde, Phineas and Ferb, the last three Star Trek movies, and Disney’s Beauty and the Beast.
            </p>
            <p>
                This year’s festival is made possible by generous donations from Hansen’s Pool  Spa and Baquacil Pool Care Systems. Participating KUSD band directors are Karl Mueller, Bradford High School; John Nepper, Harborside Academy; Kenneth Wiele, Indian Trail High School and Academy; Kathy Ripley, Tremper High School; Mike Monk, Mahone Middle School; Jeremy Kriedeman, Lance Middle School; Randy Rovik, Lincoln Middle School; Katie Poole, Bullen Middle School and Lucas Dickinson, Washington Middle School.
            </p>
            <p>
                For additional information, please contact Scott Plank, coordinator of fine arts, at 262-359-6388.
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>
            Power Up Scholarship Resource Fair is around the corner
        </title>
        <date>Monday, October 24, 2016 - 9:18am</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                On Saturday, Oct. 29, 2016, the Mary Lou and Arthur F. Mahone Fund and the Kenosha Unified School District will present the Power Up – Plug Into Your Future College and Resource Fair at the University of Wisconsin Parkside, 900 Wood Road. The resource fair is designed to expose juniors, seniors and their families to area colleges and universities while learning about financial resources available. They will have the unique opportunity to meet, network and discuss their future goals with college and business representatives from the region.
            </p>
            <p>
                As the host institution, UW-Parkside Chancellor Debbie Ford knows the importance of prospective students and their families visiting a university. “I’ll often hear family members say, ‘this is the first time I have been on a college campus.’ Close to 60 percent of our incoming students at UW-Parkside are the first in their families to attend a college or university,” Ford said. “Being here is the first step in realizing a university education is possible. Thanks to Power Up and the Scholarship Resource Fair, students and their families also see a university education is possible financially.”
            </p>
            <p>
                Workshop topics include How to Secure Scholarships, Parents Guide to College Survival, Financial Aid Tips and College Admission 101 among others. Former Mahone Fund scholarship recipients will share the benefits of the Fund’s Career Exploration Organization mentoring program and their success stories.
            </p>
            <p>
                Kenosha Unified Superintendent Dr. Sue Savaglio-Jarvis said, “Kenosha Unified is pleased to again be partnering with the Mahone Fund to bring this opportunity to our students and families. This is just one of the many steps it takes to prepare our students for success. Knowing that we have so many agencies, organizations and community partners in Kenosha that are willing to help us educate our families about college and the financial resources available to them is beyond amazing."
            </p>
            <p>
                The Power Up College and Resource fair started five years ago at Lincoln Middle School and has grown out of the parents’ desire to do what’s best for their children. “The sooner we engage our students and families in the search for post-secondary educational opportunities, the associated financial implications and the needs from our corporate and manufacturing partners, it is our belief that students will perform better in high school and therefore be college and career ready. The more we can do to help our parents access information and reduce any barriers to a quality, affordable education, the more prepared they will be in securing a bright future for their children.” said Tim Mahone, chairman, Mary Lou and Arthur F. Mahone Fund.
            </p>
            <p>
                The fair is open to minority students and students who qualify for the free and reduced lunch benefit from KUSD high edu.uwp.kusd.schools and St. Joseph Catholic Academy. Those interested in attending the event can register with their school counselor or contact the Kenosha Community Foundation office at 262-654-2412.
            </p>
            <p>
                To obtain additional college fair or vendor registration information, please visit mahonefund.org or contact Sabrina Morgan at 262-564-2362 or
                <a href="mailto:morgans@gtc.edu">morgans@gtc.edu</a>
                , or Karen Kaiser at 262-654-2412 or
                <a href="mailto:kkaiser@kenoshafoundation.org">kkaiser@kenoshafoundation.org</a>
                .
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>West Side Story opens October 28</title>
        <date>Wednesday, October 19, 2016 - 3:52pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                KUSD Theatre Arts is set to bring “West Side Story” to stage on Friday, Oct. 28, in the Bradford High School Auditorium, 3700 Washington Road. Tickets are $12 for general admission, $10 for senior citizens and $5 for students and staff.
            </p>
            <p>Show dates are:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Oct. 28 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Oct. 29 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Oct. 30 at 2 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 4, at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 5 at 7:30 p.m.</li>
                <li>Nov. 6 at 2 p.m.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                This presentation will feature students from Bradford, Indian Trail and St. Joseph High Schools. For more information, please contact Holly Stanfield at
                <a href="mailto:hstanfie@kusd.edu">hstanfie@kusd.edu</a>
                .
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>Welcome to the 60s</title>
        <date>Tuesday, October 18, 2016 - 9:16am</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                The Lance Middle School Drama Club is set to bring Hairspray Jr. to the stage on Friday, Oct. 28 and Saturday, Oct. 29 at 7 p.m. in the Lance Middle School Auditorium, 4515 80th St. Tickets are $5 for adults and $3 for students and staff.
            </p>
            <p>
                This presentation features 45 students onstage and a full student crew offstage who will bring the story to life. For more information, please contact Nina Fiegel at
                <a href="mailto:nfiegel@kusd.edu">nfiegel@kusd.edu</a>
                .
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>
            Attempted abduction notice from the Kenosha Police Department
        </title>
        <date>Thursday, October 6, 2016 - 1:46pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                On Tuesday, Oct. 4, 2016, the Kenosha Police Department took a report of an attempted child abduction. The incident occurred in the 2400 block of 52nd St. at approximately 3:40 p.m.
            </p>
            <p>
                Two students were walking east on 52nd street when an older, light blue mini van pulled up alongside them. There were two occupants in the vehicle wearing “clown masks" similar to the one used in the movie “It.” One of the suspects yelled at the two students using an expletive, “Get over here!” or “Get down!”
            </p>
            <p>
                The vehicle then turned south on 23rd Ave. and the two students ran home. There is no other description of the suspects or vehicle.
            </p>
            <p>
                Although there was no physical contact, the suspects did try to engage the students in conversation. The Kenosha Police Department asks everyone to report any suspicious activity to dispatch at 656-1234 or 9-1-1.
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>
            Bradford's Leading Ladies mentor EBSOLA-Creative Arts Little Ladies
        </title>
        <date>Thursday, October 6, 2016 - 11:47am</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                Bradford High School’s Leading Ladies group began mentoring elementary students at Edward Bain School of Language Arts-Creative Arts, naming their mentees “Little Ladies.” Twenty-two high school students committed to being mentors.
            </p>
            <p>
                “I feel that the Leading Ladies are leading the Little Ladies by example, showing they care by just being there and helping to reinforce their inner beauty,” said Kathy Harmeyer, EBSOLA-CA school guidance counselor. “The group will be a safe place to help develop their social skills and a place to develop and value their contributions.”
            </p>
            <p>
                Leading Ladies is a group of about 70 students who come together twice a month to learn more about how to turn their adversities into strengths and inspiring girls to empower them to do their best and to focus on what is important, including life skills, social skills and academic abilities.
            </p>
            <p>
                “For the high school girls, this gives them an opportunity to give back, build their resume, explore potential career interests, and earn community service hours in the process, which is a requirement for graduation,” said Cheryl J. Johnson, Bradford dean of students and Leading Ladies adviser. “Beyond that, these types of connections build self-esteem. It feels good to reach out to others and is as much a gift one gives to oneself as the gift given to the receiver. This is a win-win connection and keeps students engaged and doing positive things with their time.”
            </p>
            <p>
                The groups will meet bi-weekly with the following upcoming scheduled meeting dates:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>Monday, Oct. 17</li>
                <li>Monday, Oct. 31</li>
                <li>Monday, Nov. 14</li>
                <li>Monday, Nov. 28</li>
            </ul>
        </story>
        <image>
            http://www.kusd.edu/sites/default/files/styles/530x330/public/news/leading-ladies.jpg?itok=fxhyBjda
        </image>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>4K parent-teacher conferences</title>
        <date>Monday, October 3, 2016 - 2:24pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                4K families, please note the following schedule for parent-teacher conferences this month:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <strong>Wednesday, Oct. 26</strong>
                        – Both a.m. and p.m. sessions will be held
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <strong>Thursday, Oct. 27</strong>
                        – Only a.m. sessions will be held
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <strong>Friday, Oct. 28</strong>
                        – No 4K sessions will be held
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
        </story>
    </node>
    <node>
        <title>Social media posts - 9/30/2016</title>
        <date>Friday, September 30, 2016 - 12:07pm</date>
        <story>
            <p>
                Kenosha Unified is aware of the social media postings circulating regarding threats of clowns in our community. We have worked closely with the Kenosha Police Department to investigate the posting and found this is a trend sweeping the nation. At this time the Kenosha Police Department does not find this to be a viable threat, but asks that anyone with concerns regarding social media threats call them with details and information.
            </p>
            <p>
                Please encourage your children to avoid spreading false messages that cause unnecessary panic in our edu.uwp.kusd.schools and community. Making threats against students, staff or edu.uwp.kusd.schools is not a joking matter and individuals may face fines and/or imprisonment for their actions, whether intentional or not. Please speak to your children about the severity of making threats and the toll it will take on their future if they choose to make such a terrible choice.
            </p>
        </story>
    </node>
</node>